John Cohen collection, circa 1939-2019
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3. Still images, ca. 1954-2005
  - Subseries 3. Digitized contact sheets, ca. 1954-2005
    - Sacsamarca III (Huancavalica); Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e009.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho I; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e010.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho II; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e011.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho III; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e012.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho IV; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e013.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho V; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e014.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Huancayo VI & Santiago; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e015.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ayacucho VII on truck; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e016.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco I; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e017.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Above Cuzco Cuzco 2; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e018.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco 3 / Penny; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e019.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco 4; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e020.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco 5; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e021.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco 6; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e022.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Macchu Picchu 1; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e023.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Macchu Picchu II; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e024.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Macchu Picchu III; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e025.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Macchu Picchu IV; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e026.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Puno, train; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e027.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ocongate 1 - 1964?; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e028.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ocongate 2; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e029.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Chucuito (1); Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e030.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Chucuito 2 1964; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e031.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q 3 - July/Aug 1964 Q'eros I; Peru images from 1964, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e032.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 2 / Ocangate; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e033.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 3; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e034.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 4; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e035.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 5; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e036.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 6; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e037.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 7; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e038.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 8; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e039.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 9; Qeros 10 moved to Chicuito 2 (Dancers in Plaza); Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e040.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 11; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e041.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 12; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e042.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 13; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e043.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 14; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e044.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 15; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e045.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ccapana 1; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e046.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ccapana 2; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e047.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ccapana 3; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e048.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ccapana 4; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e049.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ccapana 5 / Extra; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e050.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima / Huayno; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e051.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima / Huayno; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e052.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ocangate, Lima, NYC; Peru images, 1964, afc2011059_ph_e053.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQ A 77 Lima; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e054.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQB77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e055.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQC77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e056.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQD77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e057.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQE77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e058.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQF77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e059.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQG77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e060.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQH77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e061.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQI77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e062.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQJ77 Lima & NYC; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e063.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - QQK77 Q'eros; Q'eros trip 4, 1977, afc2011059_ph_e064.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - London, undated, afc2011059_ph_e065a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima; Lima trip 1982, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e065b.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima (82); Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e066.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima (82); Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e067.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Rufus to Q'eros; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e068a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Rufus / Macchu Pichhu; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e068b.tif--afc2011059_ph_e069b.tif; 3 TIFF files
    - Rufus / Q'eros; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e070a.tif--afc2011059_ph_e070b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Q'eros; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e071.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Puno; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e072.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Rufus / Q'eros; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e073.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e074.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Rufus / Ollataytambo; Lima trip, 1982, afc2011059_ph_e075a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Macchu Picchu, undated, afc2011059_ph_e075b.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 84 (1); Q'eros trip 5, 1984, afc2011059_ph_e076.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 84 (2); Q'eros trip 5, 1984, afc2011059_ph_e077.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros 84 (3); Q'eros trip 5, 1984, afc2011059_ph_e078.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ancasi & Cuzco); Q'eros trip 5, undated, afc2011059_ph_e079.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e080.tif--afc2011059_ph_e084.tif; 5 TIFF files
    - Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e085.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ocangate; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e086.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima (1989); Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e087.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e088.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e089.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Q'eros; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e090.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima: Scissors dancer; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e091.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima (Julia); Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e092.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Julia & Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e093.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Film Festival, 1992, afc2011059_ph_e094.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima / Huayno; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e095.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e096.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e097.tif--afc2011059_ph_e098.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Lima (Julia I.); Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e099.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e100.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Julia / Lima; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e101.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e102.tif--afc2011059_ph_e103.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e104.tif--afc2011059_ph_e105.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Julie / Lima; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e106.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima: Charrango School; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e107.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima: Julia; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e108.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Cuzco radio; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e109.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lima: Huayno Singer; Q'eros trip 6, 1989, afc2011059_ph_e110.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Unidentified, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee001a.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee016.tif; 22 TIFF files
    - Lima - Vera Lauer, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee017a.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee017b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Lima, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee018.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Putnam Valley + Durham North Carolina, 2005, afc2011059_ph_ee019a.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee019b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Unidentified, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee020.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee028.tif; 12 TIFF files
    - Hudson River Sail "Woody Guthrie" w. Pete + Dio, Gabel + Family, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee029a.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee029b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Unidentified, undated, afc2011059_ph_ee030.tif--afc2011059_ph_ee050b.tif; 24 TIFF files
    - 3rd Ave - 1958?; Passport Portraits - JC + Robert Frank, undated, afc2011059_ph_f001.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Storefront church in Harlem, NY, ca. 1958, afc2011059_ph_f002.tif--afc2011059_ph_f019.tif; 18 TIFF files
    - Aylette, undated, afc2011059_ph_f020.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Circus - NYC, 1958, afc2011059_ph_f021.tif--afc2011059_ph_f029.tif; 8 TIFF files
    - Bruce Davidson's clown / clown BD is famous for photographing, undated, afc2011059_ph_f030.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Bruce Davidson's clown / clown BD is famous for photographing F 32, undated, afc2011059_ph_f031.tif--afc2011059_ph_f032.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Bruce Davidson's clown / clown BD is famous for photographing (Miles Forst), undated, afc2011059_ph_f033.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Circus (tent), undated, afc2011059_ph_f034.tif--afc2011059_ph_f035.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Circus Philadelphia, undated, afc2011059_ph_f037.tif--afc2011059_ph_f046.tif; 10 TIFF files
    - Motorcycles, 1958, afc2011059_ph_f047.tif--afc2011059_ph_f056.tif; 10 TIFF files
    - Yale Graduation, undated, afc2011059_ph_f082.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Protest to "Save Washington Square," undated, afc2011059_ph_f085.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Skiffle (at Folklore Center), ca. 1957, afc2011059_ph_f087.tif--afc2011059_ph_f088.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Tom's Pix NLCR - 1st Recording, undated, afc2011059_ph_f090.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Tex Logan (Mountain Music, blue- grass style w. Mike Seeger), undated, afc2011059_ph_f091.tif--afc2011059_ph_f092.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - NYC "Clancy Bros" at Folk Sing; Logan English, Billy Faier, ca. 1960-1964, afc2011059_ph_f097.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Poker Game Yale Norfolk, undated, afc2011059_ph_f101.tif--afc2011059_ph_f103.tif; 3 TIFF files
    - NYC Jazz, undated, afc2011059_ph_f105.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Washington Square & Circus (1958), 1958, afc2011059_ph_f106.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Baltimore Blue Grass Bar - Stony Mountain Boys, 1958-1959, afc2011059_ph_g001.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Baltimore Blue Grass 2 Blue Grass Bar - Stony Mountain Boys, 1958-1959, afc2011059_ph_g002.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Baltimore Blue Grass 3 Blue Grass Bar - Stony Mountain Boys; Missing Bluegrass Style Cover?, 1958-1959, afc2011059_ph_g003.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Baltimore Blue Grass 4 Blue Grass Bar--Stony Mountain Boys, 1958-1959, afc2011059_ph_g004.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Baltimore Blue Grass 5 Blue Grass Bar--Stony Mountain Boys, 1958-1959, afc2011059_ph_g005a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Woody Guthrie at Cooper Union, 1959, afc2011059_ph_g005b.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - With Jack Elliot at the Gleasons; Woody Guthrie at Cooper Union, 1959, afc2011059_ph_g005c.tif--afc2011059_ph_g005e.tif, afc2011059_ph_g005g.tif; 4 TIFF files
    - With Jack Elliot at the Gleasons; Woody Guthrie at Cooper Union; NLCR Record, 1959, afc2011059_ph_g005f.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Kentucky, 1959, afc2011059_ph_g006a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g034.tif; 40 TIFF files
    - Unidentified, undated, afc2011059_ph_g035a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g037b.tif; 5 TIFF files
    - NLCR Loft, Marvin, undated, afc2011059_ph_g038.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - NLCR by Marvin?, undated, afc2011059_ph_g039.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - 3rd Ave / May 1961 (bums & Pablo & Andrea); Studio Series, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g040.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Leo R, undated, afc2011059_ph_g041.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Mary Frank: studio, undated, afc2011059_ph_g042.tif--afc2011059_ph_g045.tif; 4 TIFF files
    - Lilly Bros & Merle Travis - Boston, ca. 1959, afc2011059_ph_g048.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - NYC - Roam; Conformity, undated, afc2011059_ph_g049.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Memphis Slim, undated, afc2011059_ph_g050.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Yale Norfolk, 1954, afc2011059_ph_g051.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Burning Building (Red Grooms), undated, afc2011059_ph_g052.tif--afc2011059_ph_g055.tif; 4 TIFF files
    - Magic Train / Happenings, undated, afc2011059_ph_g056a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g064.tif; 13 TIFF files
    - Grooms crossing 3rd Ave - (see also Mike Seeger wedding, G89) ?, undated, afc2011059_ph_g065.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pete Seeger - dancer (Carnegie?), undated, afc2011059_ph_g066.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Country Gent 1; Country Gentlemen (first recording), 1967-1970, afc2011059_ph_g067.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Country Gent 2; Country Gentlemen (first recording), 1967-1970, afc2011059_ph_g068.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Country Gent 3; Country Gentlemen (first recording), 1967-1970, afc2011059_ph_g069.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Country Gent 4; Country Gentlemen (first recording), 1967-1970, afc2011059_ph_g070.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Carriage; Pull My Daisy publicity, undated, afc2011059_ph_g074.tif--afc2011059_ph_g081.tif; 9 TIFF files
    - Swarthmore Folk Festival; Tracy, Tom, Greenbriars, undated, afc2011059_ph_g083a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g083d.tif; 4 TIFF files
    - Gandy Brodie; Studio Series, undated, afc2011059_ph_g084a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g084b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Indian Neck 1, undated, afc2011059_ph_g085.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Indian Neck 2, undated, afc2011059_ph_g086.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Indian Neck 3, undated, afc2011059_ph_g087.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Indian Neck, undated, afc2011059_ph_g088.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Seeger Wedding; Mike Marg Seeger Wedding; Also See G65, undated, afc2011059_ph_g089.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Production; Sin of Jesus, undated, afc2011059_ph_g090.tif--afc2011059_ph_g105.tif; 17 TIFF files
    - Earl Scruggs (with Mike Seeger & Tom Allen) (at New River Ranch), undated, afc2011059_ph_g106a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g107.tif; 5 TIFF files
    - Stanley Brothers at Antioch, undated, afc2011059_ph_g109.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Marge, Kim Seeger, undated, afc2011059_ph_g110.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - University of Chicago, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g111.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Los Angeles, NLCR MS, undated, afc2011059_ph_g112.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - John Stein (Baez' friend, chauffer/driver), undated, afc2011059_ph_g113.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - John Stein (Baez' friend, chauffer/driver), undated, afc2011059_ph_g114.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros I, undated, afc2011059_ph_g115.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros II, undated, afc2011059_ph_g116.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros, undated, afc2011059_ph_g117.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros IV, undated, afc2011059_ph_g118.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros V, undated, afc2011059_ph_g119.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Lilly Bros, undated, afc2011059_ph_g120.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Roscoe NY, undated, afc2011059_ph_g121.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Roscoe NY and Miss.; Lilly Bros, Ashley N.Y., undated, afc2011059_ph_g122.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove I; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g123.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove II; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g124.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g125.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove; FOTM, Ashley, Watson, Annie Bird, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g126.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove 5; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g127.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove 6; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g128.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove 7; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g129.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g130.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Union Grove; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g131.tif--afc2011059_ph_g132.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Union Grove 11; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g133.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Oak Ridge I; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g134.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Oak Ridge II; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g135.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Misc: Union Grove / Oak Ridge & Clarence Ashley (NYC). George Pegram, undated, afc2011059_ph_g136.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Misc: Grand Ole Opry (backstage), Union Grove, Lilly Brothers (Boston), Earl Scruggs & String Bean, Red Parham, undated, afc2011059_ph_g137.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ashley 1, undated, afc2011059_ph_g138.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ashley 2, undated, afc2011059_ph_g139.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Ashley 3, undated, afc2011059_ph_g140.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Doc Walsh - Wilkesboro, NC; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, undated 1961, afc2011059_ph_g141.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - W Ward I land auction with Wade Ward / Independence Virginia; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g142.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - W Ward II land auction with Wade Ward / Independence Virginia; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g143.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - W[ade] Ward III land auction with Wade Ward / Independence Virginia; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g144.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - W[ade] Ward IV land auction with Wade Ward / Independence Virginia; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g145.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Grand Ole Opry I; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g146.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Grand Ole Opry 2; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g147.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Grand Ole Opry 3; Southern Trip (1961) with Mike Seeger, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g148.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Scruggs Tour I, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g149.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - E. S. Scruggs (1961) & Pearly Davis, 1961, afc2011059_ph_g150.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Sam McGee I, undated, afc2011059_ph_g151.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Miles Forst Photos, undated, afc2011059_ph_g152.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - NLCR P. Bartok, undated, afc2011059_ph_g153.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Luray, Va 1 - first bluegrass gathering, undated, afc2011059_ph_g154.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Luray II, undated, afc2011059_ph_g155.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Luray, Va [Virginia] 3 - first bluegrass gathering, undated, afc2011059_ph_g156.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Luray IV, undated, afc2011059_ph_g157.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Luray V, undated, afc2011059_ph_g158.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Libba [Elizabeth] Cotten - 1 strip, undated, afc2011059_ph_g159a.tif--afc2011059_ph_g159b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Memphis & Willie Dixon, ca. 1959, afc2011059_ph_g160.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Gypsy Robe - for Esquire backstage Broadway, undated, afc2011059_ph_gr004.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie 1: Pull My Daisy (film planning); Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h001.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie II; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h002.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie III; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h003.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie IV; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h004.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie V; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h005.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h006.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie VII / Amram as Cowboy; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h007a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie VII / Amram as Cowboy; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h007b.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie VIII / Kerouac in coffee house; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h008.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Movie IX (film production); Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h009a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - (film production); Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h009b.tif--afc2011059_ph_h011b.tif, afc2011059_ph_h015.tif, afc2011059_ph_h017b.tif; 7 TIFF files
    - Kerouac in coffee house; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h012.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h013a.tif--afc2011059_ph_h014.tif, afc2011059_ph_h016a.tif--afc2011059_ph_h016b.tif; 5 TIFF files
    - Movie XVII (film production); Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h017a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Amram/Cowboy; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h018.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h019.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Jack & Allen Read; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h020a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Jack & Robert; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h020b.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h021.tif--afc2011059_ph_h022b.tif, afc2011059_ph_h023b.tif--afc2011059_ph_h025b.tif; 8 TIFF files
    - Music with Amram, Pablio & Rivers; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h023a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production); filed as Al Leslie After 10th St, ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h026a.tif--afc2011059_ph_h026c.tif; 3 TIFF files
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h027.tif--afc2011059_ph_h028b.tif, afc2011059_ph_h030a.tif--afc2011059_ph_h032b.tif, afc2011059_ph_h033b.tif--afc2011059_ph_h033c.tif; 10 TIFF files
    - RR Yard; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h029.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Robert with camera; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h033a.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Preacher & flag; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h034.tif--afc2011059_ph_h036.tif; 3 TIFF file
    - Chinese restaurant; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h037.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h038.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Stairwell; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h039.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Party / Crowd - 3 Verticals - text on back: "Beat Generation;" Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h040.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - Party / Crowd - LIFE mag: "Story of Beat Generation;" Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h041.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - LIFE mag: "Story of Beat Generation;" Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h042.tif--afc2011059_ph_h046.tif; 5 TIFF files
    - Jack at Chinese / Robert & Gregory Corso; Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h047.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - (film production); Pull My Daisy (planning & production), ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h048a.tif--afc2011059_ph_h048b.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - Allen Ginsberg at Columbia University; Pull My Daisy publicity - carriage, ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h049.tif--afc2011059_ph_h051.tif; 3 TIFF files
    - Rex Roth at club; Pull My Daisy publicity - carriage, ca. 1957-1959, afc2011059_ph_h052.tif--afc2011059_ph_h053.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h054.tif--afc2011059_ph_h071.tif; 18 TIFF files
    - Window view; 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h072.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - (Cedar & Exterior); 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h073.tif; 1 TIFF file
    - 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h074.tif--afc2011059_ph_h075.tif; 2 TIFF files
    - The Artist's Club; 10th Street Galleries, undated, afc2011059_ph_h076.tif--afc2011059_ph_h078.tif; 3 TIFF files